{
    "id": "bcd55d2aabd243dbbc9fab6914855953",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was let off …………………. he would not repeat the offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "on condition that",
                "in order that",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He wore a coat ………………… he might not catch cold.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in order that",
                "provided that",
                "on condition that",
                "so as to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been raining continuously ………………….. yesterday morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "from",
                "since",
                "ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The conference will take place between the 10th …………………. the 16th of June.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "through",
                "to",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the kind of music that I like to listen .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "from",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is the man that I was talking to you …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "about",
                "with",
                "None of these"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. my best efforts, I could not win the election.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "By means",
                "Owing to",
                "In spite of",
                "On behalf of"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Pay your fee on time lest you ……………….. be fined.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He ……………….. only say what he wants and it will be granted.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need",
                "would",
                "could",
                "might"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know if we can fully confide ..................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "in",
                "at",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}